undercovertourist.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy | No spam, just common sense | Undercover Tourist

### Last Updated 05/25/2018

No spam, just common sense and trust ...

  * Your comfort in dealing with us is a priority, which is why common sense is used when handling your personal details.

  * Personally identifiable information is never sold or leased to any third parties.

We want to ensure that you will feel comfortable in recommending us to your friends & family.

We believe it is of the utmost importance in developing a relationship with our visitors to clearly set forth our policies & practices so that you will have an enjoyable experience.

Your use of UndercoverTourist.com is governed by the policies, terms & conditions set forth below:

UndercoverTourist.com policy is to respect & protect the privacy of our visitors. This policy statement explains what information we gather from your visit to our Website & how such information may be used.

### Security

UndercoverTourist.com has taken great care in providing secure transmission of your personal & private information. We use reasonable security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information collected via our website and under our control so that you can feel comfortable and secure when using our website. A green lock icon will appear in the left-hand side of your browser window when you enter pages on our website secured through Secure Sockets Layers (SSL), the best encryption software in the industry. We also use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving orders on our website. Notwithstanding the precautions that we take, we cannot guarantee the security of information that you transmit to us, and shall not be liable for any failure to safeguard your information, whether inadvertent or otherwise.

### Data Collection

InsiderGuide.com, LLC dba UndercoverTourist.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this website. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

By using this site, you signify your assent to the UndercoverTourist.com Privacy Policy.

If you do not agree with this policy, please do not visit our site. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

We will strive to protect your personal information, however InsiderGuide.com, LLC cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services & you do so at your own risk.

Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

By submitting information to us, you consent to its collection and use by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Users have the option of discontinuing participation in our mailing lists or programs, or editing their personally identifiable information by contacting us. (See “Opt-in/Opt-out,” below.)

### Ordering Information & Contact Information

Our website uses various order forms for you to request information, products & services.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: When you visit the site, we collect some basic information that does not identify individual users. This includes pages visited, types of products purchased, and feedback from our visitors, as well as location data, logs and other communication data, and information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

Third party advertising companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. These third party cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. For more information about cookies and how to opt out of third party data collection, please refer to the section entitled 'Cookies' within this policy.

Personally Identifiable Information: When you make a purchase on this website, we collect contact information, such as your name, mailing and or email address and financial information (your credit card number, expiration date, billing address) to process your order. We do not store your credit card number. Contact information from an order form is used for billing purposes and to fill your order. If we have difficulty processing an order, we may use the contact information to communicate with you. If you actively request information from us (an example of a request would be if you actively checked a box to sign up for our mailing list) we will respond to your request.

The contact information may be used to contact you when necessary regarding your order. We may send you information about our company if you actively request it. The financial information that is collected to process your request for products & services will be used for the sole purpose of billing the consumer for products purchased from Undercover Tourist.com and will not be shared with third parties who are not involved with the transaction.

We implement reasonable security measures to protect the financial information you provide to us in conjunction with your purchases from our website. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.

### Feedback Information

UndercoverTourist.com forms & feedback sections may request that you give us contact information such as your name, mailing and email address, as well as demographic information, such as your age & gender.

### General Information

Information provided by you, such as your email address, via email inquiries to UndercoverTourist.com are used only to respond to your inquiries & and are never shared, sold or leased to third parties.

### Online Survey Information 

To participate in online surveys, customers may be required to supply personally identifiable information. UndercoverTourist.com utilizes the information provided subject to usage as described in “Data Collection,” above, and to send that user any compensation promised in exchange for completing the survey.

### Account Registration Information 

Account registration areas on our website may require users to provide personally identifiable information, which is subject to usage as described in “Data Collection,” above.

### Contest/Sweepstakes Information 

Participation in contests, sweepstakes, raffles, games or similar promotions sponsored by UndercoverTourist.com also requires the disclosure of personally identifiable information. We may share that information with third-party sponsors of the contests, sweepstakes, raffles, games or similar promotions. This information is subject to usage outlined in “Data Collection,” above. In addition, you should carefully review the rules of each contest, sweepstakes, raffle, game or similar promotion in which you participate. The extent that the terms and conditions of those rules concerning treatment of your personally identifiable information conflict with this Privacy Policy, the terms and conditions of those rules will control.

### Cookies and Other Technologies

We collect non-personal information about our website traffic and usage patterns from technology such as Cookies and Web Beacons. Cookies are small text files that help us to personalize the content of our website. Web Beacons are electronic files used to track your navigation on a website or collection of sites, the completion of transactions, submittal of applications and browsing behavior.

We use cookies and other tracking technology to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, and keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use IP addresses to analyze trends, help us administer the website, track the movement of visitors, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are permitted to use the information collected on our behalf to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. However, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. If you delete your Cookies, use a different browser, or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out choice.

### Disclosure for Legal Purposes 

We may be required to share your personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants or orders. If we are legally required to do so, or, in good faith believe that we are legally required to do so, we will obey the law. In addition, we reserve the right to use, disclose and share your personal and non-personal information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or as otherwise required by law.

### Disclaimer Concerning Third Parties 

We may provide certain personally identifiable information to our partners. Furthermore, we may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include financial institutions, consumer e-mail service providers, web data tracking specialists and reservation booking engines. Such third parties may be provided with access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any other purpose.

### Special Note Concerning Persons Under The Age of 18

Our online services are not directed toward persons under the age of 18, and we request that persons under the age of 18 not provide personally identifiable information to us.

### IP Address

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet provider whenever you're surfing the Web.

InsiderGuide.com, LLC collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to audit the use of our Site.

We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that your session will be logged, but you are anonymous to us.

We may use your IP addresses in cooperation with your Internet provider to identify you if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use or to protect our service, sites, customers, or others.

### Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, etc., we ask for contact information such as name, and e-mail address to provide these communications. Because we respect your privacy, we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the choice and opt-out section below.

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send you an e-mail. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

### Opt-In/Opt-Out

We welcome your feedback. If you have questions, complaints, or if you would like to express a concern, remove yourself from our mailing lists, change your personally identifiable information, or have your personally identifiable information removed from our systems, please contact us by email, phone or mail: 

Email: info@undercovertourist.com

Phone: 1-800-846-1302

Mail: P.O. Box 250676, Daytona Beach, FL 32125.

Or you may simply reach out to us through our website: Contact Us.

Please note that any requests to remove your personally identifiable information from our mailing list, or to change your contact information, may take a certain amount of time to process. 

### Changes to This Policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy, and any of our policies or procedures concerning the treatment of information collected through the site, without prior notice. You can determine when this privacy policy was last revised by referring to date at the top of this page. Any changes to our privacy policy will become effective upon posting of the revised policy on the Internet, accessible through our Website. Use of the site following such changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised policy then in effect. We encourage you to periodically review our privacy policy to ensure familiarity with our most current version.

UNDERCOVERTOURIST.COM RESERVES THE RIGHT TO UPDATE THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ITS DISCRETION. ANY CHANGES WILL BE POSTED ON OUR WEBSITE. OUR RIGHT TO USE YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AND NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION WILL BE BASED ON APPLICABLE LAW AND THE PRIVACY POLICY IN EFFECT AT THE TIME THE INFORMATION IS COLLECTED.
